How are you?
Jeff Klein here vodka connoisseur and resident bartender here at Beak's Old Florida in St. Petersburg.
And I'm going to tell you about the best Smirnoff vodka.
Now there's a lot of different flavors and Smirnoff has been around for awhile obviously.
My favorite though is the classic.
Just your red label eighty proof Smirnoff vodka.
It's consistently ranked in the top ten over the past, over the past decade.
And there's a clean crisp flavor to it that can not be beat.
Now if you are somebody who cares for maybe a little something sweeter when they are drinking I would recommend the blueberry flavored Smirnoff.
It's a nice flavor, it's not to sweet and it's extremely versatile.
Whether with cranberry juice, soda water or just by itself on the rocks or as a martini.
It gives you that little bit of flavor while keeping that crisp vodka that you like.
So once again my name is Jeff Klein vodka connoisseur and bartender here at Beak's Old Florida and that's the best Smirnoff vodka.